You probably think college students are experts at sleeping but parties,
preparations for tests, personal problems, and general stress can rag a student's
sleep habits. You probably think college students are experts at sleeping but
parties, preparations for tests, personal problems, and general stress can rag a
student's sleep habits.
You probably think college students are experts at sleeping but parties,
preparations for tests, personal problems, and general stress can rag a student's
sleep habits. which can be bad for the body and the mind.
Texas Tech University is even offering a class called Improving Your Sleep Habits.
which can be bad for the body and the mind.
People suffering from sleep loss are at increased risk from obesity, psychological
problems, and car crashes.
Students who don't get enough sleep have poor attendance and lower grades.
On top of all that, a new study published in the journal Learning and Memory...